To push to GitHub, run these commands in PowerShell:

git remote remove origin 2>$null
git remote add origin https://github.com/YOUR_GITHUB_USERNAME/true-peptide-labs.git
git branch -M main
git push -u origin main

Replace YOUR_GITHUB_USERNAME with your actual GitHub username.

If you get authentication error, use a GitHub Personal Access Token (classic) as password when prompted.

After successful push, go to Vercel and redeploy or check the production branch is set to "main".
